{"data":[{"question":"We don't usually go there now but we ________ there quite often.","a":"used to going","b":"used to go","c":"use to go","d":"use to going","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He is not ________ in a tent.","a":"used to sleeping","b":"use to sleep","c":"used to sleep","d":"use to sleeping","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We are not ________ in such a noisy place.","a":"used to live","b":"use to live","c":"use to living","d":"used to living","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I still haven't got ________ in this huge city.","a":"use to living","b":"used to living","c":"use to live","d":"used to live","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: don't\/doesn't\/can't\/didn't\/hasn't\/haven't get\/got + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"His grandparents ________ to school ten kilometers away on foot.","a":"used to go","b":"use to go","c":"used to going","d":"use to going","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When she was young she used to ________ up quite early.","a":"to get","b":"geting","c":"get","d":"getting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He is broke but he is used ________ money.","a":"to have no","b":"to having no","c":"to have not","d":"not to have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We are not used ________ rich.","a":"to be","b":"be","c":"to being","d":"being","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm not ________ up so early.","a":"used to getting","b":"use to getting","c":"used to get","d":"use to get","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I usually go on Saturdays. I didn't ________ before.","a":"used to go","b":"use to go","c":"used to going","d":"use to going","answer":"2","explain":"- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true\n\n-Negative  form:  S +didn't + use to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}